Guide to the Charles Baptie photograph collection, 1917-1995
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
The Charles Baptie photograph collection
1917-1995
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Charles Baptie, 1914-2000
C0032
26 linear feet (24 document boxes, 35 3-ring photo boxes, and 12 oversize boxes)
Mid-20th century photographs of Washington, D.C., area landmarks, including Gunston Hall, the White House, and embassies; local businesses, including Texaco stations and Hot Shoppes; and more common subjects, like artwork, animals, nature, or people. These images are in several formats: negatives, slides, prints, and publications.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated in several stages by Charles Baptie and J. Roger Bentley. Charles Baptie, in November 1993, donated GMU materials and other material relating to Northern Virginia. He donated 2.4 linear feet of negatives in July 1994. He donated more photographic negatives and other material in September 1994. In May 2002, J. Roger Bentley donated 1900 negatives, 1,400 photographs, and some publication materials. The next year, May 2003, he donated approximately 2,000 negatives, slides, and photographs, as well as pamphlets, postcards, news clippings and other documents.
Biographical Information
Charles Baptie, a photographer, printer, and publisher, was born in Munhall, PA on March 13, 1914. Early in life, Baptie became interested in photography and airplanes, interests that would eventually lead to him becoming a photographer and public relations agent for Capital Airlines. His camera recorded the life of the airline for many years. When Capital Airlines merged with United Airlines, Baptie left the company and formed his own business, Charles Baptie Studios, Inc.
While operating his own studio, Baptie provided photographs for more than fifty books and other publications, including: Capital Airlines: A Nostalgic Flight Into the Past, Great Houses of Washington, Camera on Assignment (with Ollie Atkins), the sixteen volume Encyclopedia of United States History, Guest House of the Presidents, the story of the Blair Lee House, and Mid the Hills of Pennsylvania. As a photojournalist, Baptie covered feature stories for leading magazines and other news publications. Over the course of his journalistic career, Baptie met and photographed many world leaders and public figures. He passed away in 2000.
Scope and Content
The Charles Baptie Photograph Collection contains color prints and negatives of Gunston Hall, the home of George Mason; color transparencies from the Encyclopedia of United States History; color transparencies and prints from the Great Houses of Washington, D.C.; black & white negatives of the Washington metropolitan area; and photographs of George Mason College. There are, in addition, aerial photographs, photographs of malaria prevention overseas, and publicity photographs for various publications. Also included in this collection are photographs pertaining to the childrens' book, Herkie the Pup, written by Charles Baptie. The total volume of the collection is 26 linear feet, consisting of 24 document boxes, 35 3-ring photo boxes, and 12 oversize boxes.
Series 1 is a group of images of buildings, both interior and exterior, including facades of famous houses and embassies around DC as well as images of the interior decorations; also included are images of churches, DC monuments, hotels, restaurants, schools, laboratories, service stations, theaters, hospitals, and personal homes.
Series 2 consists of images of the Belgian, Brazilian, French, Irish, Mexican, Peruvian, Spanish, and Turkish embassies; most of these items are also found in series 1.
Series 3 contains images of artwork, including of paintings, sculptures, dolls, trophies, and architecture; also images of artwork used for publications such as a baseball book, an Encyclopedia of American History, a History of the Civil War, and a Northern Virginia guidebook.
Series 4 is for Publications for which Baptie either provided photos or printed at his studio including brochures and pamphlets, guide books, logos, small print books, magazines, and poetry collections.
Series 5 shows images of Texaco stations in the area, both on the ground and in the air throughout the Washington, D.C., area included are aerial views and on-the-ground images, as well as plans, blueprints, portraits, and vehicles.
Hot Shoppes restaurant photos make up Series 6, Hot Shoppes were a chain of restaurant owned by the Marriott Company and the series includes images of food, their Airline service, their kitchens, and the dining rooms of the restaurants.
Series 7 includes photographs of D.C. monuments and landmarks including Capitol Hill, the Lincoln Memorial, the Jefferson Memorial, the Washington Monument, the White House, and Mount Vernon.
Series 8 contains images from several other series that happen to be aerial shots, as well as general aerial views from around the country; images of nearby locations include Alexandria, Annandale, Texaco service stations, construction sites, DC monuments, Gunston Hall, Sully Plantation, and the Potomac River.
Series 9 consists of nature scenes, such as trees, mountains, clouds, gardens, fireworks, sunsets, clouds, bodies of water, landscapes, and cemeteries.
Series 10 contains maps and building plans, such as blueprints or architectural renderings, specific topics include St. Agnes School, Baltimore, Texaco, Hazelton labs, Woodbridge Toll Center, and Fairfax Hills.
People make up the subject of Series 11, where the people are doing something else or just taking a portrait. Many photos have unidentified subjects, while others show notable Washingtonians and politicians, athletes, scientists, wedding guests, presidents, actors, the National Symphony, and military leaders.
Series 12 consists of pictures of food from restaurants, Hot Shoppes, and holiday events.
Series 13 is made up of museum exhibits and artifacts including the Star Spangled Banner, dolls, and various Smithsonian objects and exhibits.
Series 14 documents various animals including monkeys, horses, birds, bees, cattle, dogs, hippopotamuses, snakes, butterflies and animals for scientific testing.
Series 15 shows different types of technology such as science labs, computers, a space shuttle, factories, and a camera.
George Mason College is featured in Series 16 with images of athletic teams, staff members, buildings, campus, students, graduations, George Mason Day, and printed materials.
Series 17 includes pictures of vehicles, such as cars, baby carriage, planes, trains, ships, helicopters and bicycles.
Series 18 consists of images from Gunston Hall, the historical home of George Mason. Images in the series include the Mason coat of arms, publications, postcard images, aerial views, and a car show hosted by Gunston Hall.
Series 19 is consists of images of international subjects taken during Baptie's many travels, including various settings in Central America, like Brazil, Honduras, and Ecuador; and other locations, such as Paris or India.
Series 20 is made up of documents consisting of correspondence between Charles Baptie and others about photograph orders and publications.
Finally, Series 21 contains electronic media, specifically a number of 5 1/4 inch floppy discs used for a program called Wordstar.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into 21 series.
Series 1: Buildings: Interior and Exterior, 1947-1975
Series 2: Embassies, 1950s-1970s
Series 3: Art, 1947-1975
Series 4: Publications, 1942-1994
Series 5: Texaco Stations, 1950-1972
Series 6: Hot Shoppes, 1948-1953
Series 7: Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1944-1991
Series 8: Aerial Photographs, 1934-1991
Series 9: Nature, 1917-1988
Series 10: Maps and Building Plans, 1941-1973
Series 11: People, 1944-1976
Series 12: Food, 1950s-1960s
Series 13: Museum Exhibits, 1952-1970s
Series 14: Animals, 1946-1980s
Series 15: Technology, 1948-1974
Series 16: George Mason College, 1959-1976
Series 17: Vehicles, 1946-1995
Series 18: Gunston Hall, 1960s-1993
Series 19: International, 1958-1989
Series 20: Correspondence, 1955-1990s
Series 21: Electronic Media, 1970s-1980s
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds the the and the.
Index Terms
Persons:
Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1890-1969--Photographs.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972--Photographs.
Corporate Names:
George Mason University--Photographs.; Gunston Hall (Va.)--Photographs.
Geographical Names:
Mall, The (Washington, D.C.)--Photographs.; Washington (D.C.)--Photographs.; Virginia, Northern--Photographs.; Ecuador--Photographs.; Honduras--Photographs.
Subjects:
Buildings--Photographs.; Drive-in restaurants--Photographs.; Embassy buildings--Washington (D.C.)--Photographs.; Monuments and memorials--Washington (D.C.)--Photographs.; Nature--Photographs.; Service stations--Photographs.; Technology--Photographs.
Document Types:
Aerial photographs.; Negtaives.; Photographic prints.; Portraits.; Slides.
Contents List
- Series 1: Buildings: Interiors and Exteriors, 1947-1975
  This series contains photographic prints, negatives and slides that show various building interiors and exteriors. Some of these photographs appear in other series based on the image. Images include facades of famous houses and embassies around Washington, D.C., as well as images of the interior decorations. Also included are images of churches, Washington, D.C., monuments, hotels, restaurants, schools, laboratories, service stations, theaters, hospitals, and personal homes.
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Anderson house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Arts club
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Bacon house (negatives)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Robert Lou Bacon
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Belgian Embassy
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Belmont house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Blair house (negatives)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Brazilian Embassy
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Cosmos Club
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Decatur house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Dumbarton House
  - Embassies and Houses, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Dumbarton Oaks
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Evermay
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Firenze house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 15)
    French Embassy
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Hillwood
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 17)
    International Eastern Star Temple
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Irish Embassy
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Kreegar house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Laird house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 21)
    The Lindens
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Meridian house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Mexican Embassy (1 of 2)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Mexican Embassy (2 of 2)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Morris house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Senator Claiborne Pell's house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Peruvian Embassy
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Post (Marjorie Merriweather) house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Prospect house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Spanish Embassy (1 of 2)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Spanish Embassy (2 of 2)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Stanley house, Tryon Place
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Tryon Place
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Tudor place
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Turkish Embassy (1 of 2)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Turkish Embassy (2 of 2)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Woodrow Wilson house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Worthington house
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 13)
    unidentified
  - Alsop House, Jan 1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Image of Alsop house. (negatives)
  - Joe Alsop's Georgetown House, Jan 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Interior images of Joe Alsop's Georgetown House. (negatives)
  - Arlington Hospital, 1 June 1954 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Image of Arlington Hospital, Arlington High School. (negatives)
  - Bell Telephone Company, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Image of Bell Telephone Company Building. (negatives)
  - Blakestone Island, 15 September 1954 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Images of buildings on Blakestone Island. (negatives)
  - Butterfly Hill, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Images of Butterfly Hill. (negatives)
  - Capitol, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Images of Capitol Hill. (negatives)
  - Cathedral Series, July 1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Images of cathedrals. (negatives)
  - Cavlier Hotel Series, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Image of Cavalier Hotel. (negatives)
  - Christ Church, 9 November 1950 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Images of Christ Church. (negatives)
  - Columbus Fountain, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Images of buildings such as Columbus Fountain. (negatives)
  - Lock at Cumberland, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Images of buildings at the lock at Cumberland. (negatives)
  - Dupont Circle, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Images of buildings at Du Pont Circle. (negatives)
  - Washington Monument, 4 June 1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Images of The Washington Monument with fireworks. (negatives)
  - Georgetown, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Images of buildings in Georgetown. (negatives)
  - Hogates, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Images of buildings at Hogates. (negatives)
  - Jefferson Village, 6 September 1950 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Images of buildings in Jefferson Village. (negative)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 10 February 1956 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Images of the Jefferson Memorial. (negatives)
  - Library of Congress, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Images of Library of Congress. (negatives)
  - Ossian Hall, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Images of Ossian Hall.
  - Riggs Bank, 12 September 1953 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Interior images of Riggs Bank. (negatives)
  - St. Agnes School, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Images of St. Agnes School. (negatives)
  - Schools, 20 July 1952 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Images of school buildings. (negatives)
  - Supreme Court, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Images of Supreme Court building. (negatives)
  - Taft Bridge, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Images of buildings around Taft Bridge. (negatives)
  - Union Station, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Images of Union Station. (negatives)
  - Views along Route 40, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Images of buildings along Route 40. (negatives)
  - Washington Scenes, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Images of buildings in Washington, D.C.
  - Art Masters, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Exterior and interior images of Art Master's. (negatives)
  - Cemetery Series, 15 July 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Exterior and interior images of a cemetery. (negatives)
  - Churches, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Exterior and interior images of churches. (with negatives)
  - Hotels and Motels Series, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Exterior and interior images of hotels and motels.
  - Houses, 1950s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Exterior and interior images of houses. (with negatives)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Exterior and interior images of miscellaneous buildings.
  - Restaurants and Food, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Exterior and interior images of restaurants.
  - Schools, 1950s-1960s-1970s (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Exterior and interior images of schools. (with negatives)
  - American Association of Nursery Men, 26 October 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    American Association of Nursery Men (1 of 2), buildings. (negatives)
  - American Association of Nursery Men, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 3)
    American Association of Nursery Men (2 of 2), buildings. (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Voices of America, buildings (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1954, 1956, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    American Weekly (1 of 4), buildings (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1953, 1957, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    American Weekly (2 of 4), buildings (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1950, 1956, 1959, 1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    American Weekly (3 of 4), buildings (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1956, 1960, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    American Weekly (4 of 4), buildings (negatives)
  - Allen Dickey, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Allen Dickey, Architect, buildings (negatives)
  - Wills and Van Metre, January 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Wills and Van Metre buildings (negatives)
  - Hazelton Labs, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 1, 2, 6)
    Building interiors of Hazelton Labs. (negatives)
  - Texaco, 1950s-1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 1-43)
    Photographs of the interior of a Texaco station, as well as the exteriors of several more locations. (with negatives)
  - Texaco, 1950s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 1-54)
    Photographs of the exteriors of several Texaco gas stations.
  - Miscellaneous building interiors, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Photographs of miscellaneous building interiors. (negatives)
  - Mayo Stontz, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Photographs of building interiors. (negatives)
  - Miscellaneous Service Stations, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Photographs of the exterior of miscellaneous service stations. (negatives)
  - Wastewater Treatment Plant, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Photographs of a wastewater treatment plant.
  - Harry Clarkson Home, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Photographs of Harry Clarkson's home. (negative)
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Building being constructed.
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Photographs of various buildings. (with slides)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Photographs of various buildings.
  - Fairfax Hospital, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Photographs of Fairfax Hospital. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Bootery Shop, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Photographs of a bootery shop. (negatives)
  - Hawkins Motor Company, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Photographs of the Hawkins Motor Company building. (negatives)
  - Arlex Esso Service Station, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Photographs of Arlex Esso Service Station. (negatives)
  - Church of St. Clement, 1960s (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Exterior view of St. Clement church.
  - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Photographs of various buildings around town. (negatives)
  - photo albums, 1960s (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Photographs of hotel rooms inside and out and of various buildings. (with negatives)
  - Photo Album, 1950s-1960s (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Photographs of various building interior and exteriors, as well as kitchens.
  - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - St. John's Church, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Photographs of the inside of St. John's Church. (with negatives)
  - Photographs from Shirlington Photographers, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Photographs of Virginia Theatre.
  - Shirlington Photographs, 1960s (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Photographs of various building interiors. (with negatives)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    Postcards of St. John's Church and Rive Gauche Cafe.
  - Trip photos, 1970s-1980s (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Photographs of buildings while on a trip.
  - Photo Album, 1950s-1960s (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Photographs of building interior and exteriors.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    Negatives of the exterior and interior of several buildings: Little Theatre; DAR; Blair House; Statler Hotel; Sand Meridian; Shrine of Immaculate Conception; Harvey Rest; Holiday Inn; and Kenmore's House (Fredericksburg, VA).
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 26)
    Negatives that contain images of building interiors and exteriors of these subjects: Mrs. Hunt; Riverside Garden; Waynewood; Woodlawn; Kurty; and Alexandria Hospital.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 27)
    Interior images of Gunston Hall and Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 28)
    Images of building exteriors and interiors of houses, tele tech, Yates restaurant, hotels, restaurants, street house, embassies, and Firenze house. (with negatives)
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 29)
    Building interiors and exteriors from amongst toy making, film set, Ecuador, malaria prevention, Honduras, and US generals prints.
  - Buildings, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s, 1988 (Box 30)
    Building interiors and exteriors within the following print subjects: construction sites; room interiors; apartment plans; building facades; river; aerial Washington, D.C., monuments; Niagara Falls; Hot Shoppes; fireworks; factory; and World War Two scenes.
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 31)
    Prints and negatives of building interiors and exteriors within the following subjects: scenic mountain views; Ecuador; aerial Washington, D.C., views; building exteriors; a film set; toy making; people; cattle; food; flowers; and Buddy Dean band.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 32)
    Images of the exterior and interior of hotels, restaurants, and embassies.
  - Buildings, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s (Box 33)
    Building interiors and exteriors within this box containing: handwritten notes; Mise; Sully Plantation; Air Force; Plate; President Truman; St. Petersburg; Baseball Team; Kid's haircut; White House; Misc. Vacation Resort; Adolf Hitler; and L. Campaign. (with negatives)
  - Buildings, 1957-1974 (Box 34)
    Images of building interiors and interiors of Woodlawn; St. John's Church; and National Biological lab. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1950s (Box 35)
    Negatives of building interiors and exteriors of Mt. Vernon, Mexico Chapala Church, Riggs Seria, Phil Sern Co., Carlyle home, Hostess Cox Series, Farly, Silver Spring store, Woodlawn, St. Clements, Continental Room, House military affair, Briefing room in ATC, Officers club, and Coast Guard lab.
  - Buildings, 1964, 1967 (Box 36)
    Negatives of Interior and exterior images of Fairfax Hospital.
  - Buildings, 1971-1990 (Box 37)
    Building interiors and exteriors from the following topics: vacation, Space shuttle launch, aircraft and hot air balloons, Baptie at home, architectural interiors and exteriors, Washington, D.C., monuments, Mt. Vernon, and Gunston Hall. (with negatives)
  - Buildings, 1949-1972 (Box 38)
    Images of building interiors and exteriors are found within the following picture subjects: Vepco Fire, hospital campaign, Alexandria, Fairfax Hills, Mining Company, Windsor Park hotel, Chuck Baptie, Homestead PA and map, Washington Hebrew Congregation, Tom Lawson, Cowboy Ray Allen, Harod the Great, Masonic Temple - Alexandria, Cathedral, St. Clements Church, Butterfly prints, Great Falls air NG, aerials of Gunston Hall, Fairfax hospital (1972-6-21), Nepal, Alexandria Hospital, boat, Gunston Hall car show (1993)
  - Buildings, 1959-1975 (Box 39)